Guide to the Elmer Holmes Bobst Collection 1862-1978 MSS 67 MSS 067
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Awards, Plaques, Medals, Certificates and Honors.
  - Subseries A: Boxed Awards.
    - Lancaster, Pa. J.A. Businessman Award. 1974 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania Ambassador Award. 1951 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Rider College, New Jersey. Honorary L.L.D. [2 certificates], undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Treasury War Finance Committee, New Jersey. Certificates, 4th through 6th War Loan, 1944. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Treasury War Finance Committee. Certificate in recognition of distinguished records, War Loans 1 through 6. 1944 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - World War II Veteran Association. Advisory Member. 1944 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Treasury. [2 citations] 1943. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - American Cancer Society Citation, 1971. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Canadian Foundation for the Advancement of Pharmacy, 1960. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Lancaster Rotary Club. Pennsylvania Ambassador Award. 1951 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - American Physicians Art Association. Special Award. 1965 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Mario Negri Institute Foundation. Certificate of Achievement. 1978 (See also: Folder 5). (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Papanicolaou Cancer Research Institute. Founders Certificate. 1977 (See also: Folder 5). (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Various medals: Mario Negri Institute Foundation, 1978; Papanicolauou Cancer Research Institute, 1977; Chung-Ang University, Seoul, Korea, 1978., 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Subseries B: Framed Awards on Display.
    - U.S. Treasury Award. War Finance Committee, Newark, N.J. Certificate of Merit for Patriotic Service. 1945 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Red Cross of Greater New York. War Fund. Certificate of Honor. 1944 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Hahnemann Medical College, Philadelphia. Pa. Honorary Doctor of Science Degree. 1957 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - New York City. John V. Lindsay, Mayor. Citation for Distinguished and Exceptonal Service. 1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - New York City. Abraham D. Beame, Mayor. Certificate of Appreciation on his 90th Birthday. 1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania State Certificate of Registered Pharmacist. 1905 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - U.S. War Production Board. Certificate in recognition of Elmer Holmes Bobst's contribution to the war effort. n.d., undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - American Cancer Society. Special Citation for Elmer Holmes Bobst's vision in his reorganization of the Society and for his "spiritual and business leadership" in the affairs of the Society. 1959 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - American Society of Contemporary Medicine and Surgery. Distinguished Service Award. 1972 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Series IV: Articles, Press Releases, Speeches and Correspondence.
  Box 1: Articles about Elmer Holmes Bobst, 1921-1989; Box 2: Articles, etc. written by Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1936-1978; Box 3: Obituary and Memorial Service, August-September 1978. See also: Series I. Album 4. Editorials, ca. 1940; Album 4b. Letters to stockholders, ca. 1940; Album 11. A Sketchy Record of our Peregrinations Aboard Alisa IV. 1951; Series VI, Oversize Item 4 for Obituary in The Record Express, Lititz, Pa. August 10, 1978.
  - Newspaper clippings and press releases, 1921-1954. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings and press releases, 1955-1956. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings and press releases, 1957-1959. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings and press releases, 1960-1966. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings and press releases, 1967-1973. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hoffman-LaRoche, 25th Anniversary Brochure. 1930 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Article: Elmer Bobst-Vitamin King, by Meador Wright. Monthly Magazine of the Oranges and Montclair. Apr. 1943 p.11. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Elmer Bobst Heads Warner, The Apothecary, Jan. 1946 p.1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst, The Warner Orbis, Jan. 1946 p.1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Elmer Bobst Started his Career in a Drugstore, National Association of Retail Druggists. Journal, Feb. 4, 1946. p.242., undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Medicine, Time, Apr. 26, 1946. p.76. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Life Begins at 60, Time, Feb. 11, 1952. p.38. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Men of Letters, Elmer H. Bobst, Better Impressions, 1st Quarter, 1952. p.8. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Merger-Minded Warner-Lambert, Fortune, Oct. 1955, p.43. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Elmer H. Bobst Lauded by Speakers, The Bronze Mortar, (Columbia University College of Pharmacy) June 1957. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Viewpoint Marketing, Newsweek, Sep. 1, 1958, p.37. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - American Cancer Society Advertisement. NY Times Magazine. Mar. 27, 1960. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Press Release: Warner-Lambert and 3M Co. merger possible. Aug. 17, 1960. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Opportunity Still Knocks. Horatio Alger Awards Publication, 1965. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bobst Dedication, Hahnemann Alumni News, Fall, 1967. p1. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Warner-Lambert, the buy it" Company," Television Age, Nov. 7, 1967. p.21. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - And Co-starring Pat Nixon, NY Times Magazine, Sep. 11, 1970. p.27. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Nixon's 36 Best Friends, Washingtonian, Dec. 1970 p.62. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Hester, James. New York University, the Urban University Coming of Age. (Newcomen Address, 1970) NY: Newcomen Society, 1971., 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Nixon's Inner Circle of Businessmen, Business Week, Jul. 31, 1971. p.52 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - How Splendid the Day, biography of Elmer Holmes Bobst by Robert Alberts. Publisher's announcement. New York University Press Fall Catalogue, 1971. p.76. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Nixon's Private Circle, U.S. News and World Report, May 7, 1973. p.25. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Faster! Faster! - Elmer Bobst, Palm Beach Life. Aug. 1973 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Top 20 Addresses [in New York], Town and Country. Sep. 1973 p.40. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Annals of Law, The New Yorker, Apr. 17, 1989, p.90. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Dedication of the Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, New York University. (Clippings, guest lists, programs, etc.) Oct.-Dec. 1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Gala Bobst Library Open House. (Invitations, clippings, brochures, correspondence, etc.) Oct. 1973 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Address: In honor of Dr. Barell. Basel, Feb. 15, 1936. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Address: Hoffmann-La Roche 25th Anniversary, 1936. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Address: Roche Employees, 1942. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Address: Roche Employees, 1946. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Address: Federal Reserve Bank Savings Bond Dinner, 1946. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Address: Security Loan Campaign Dinner, 1948. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Address: Lititz High School Alumni, June 1948. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Address: American Pharmaceutical Manufacturers, 1948. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Address: Connecticut Cancer Society Campaign Dinner, 1949. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Address: U.S. Savings Bonds, New Jersey Division, 1949. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Address: Lititz High School Alumni, 1951. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Address: The Warner-Hudnut Story, 1952. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Address: Advertising Women's Club of New York, 1952. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Address: "The Realshav Razor" Introduction, 1953. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Address: Lititz, PA. High School Ground-breaking, 1955. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Address. Fairleigh Dickenson College, 1955. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Address: On achieving life membership in the Canadian Foundation for the Advancement of Pharmacy, 1960. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Address: Dedication of the Elmer Holmes Bobst Institute of Clinical Research, 1967. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Article: "Detailing." Druggists Circular, Oct. 1934 p.16. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Article: "His Biggest Fee." Offprint of an editorial from the Roche Review. 1939 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Article: Three Tales Told of Your Doctor, 1941. Reprinted from Roche Review. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Article: "Acorns and Oaks," 1943. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Article: Introduction to Standard Bearers, Jan. 1946 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Article: "Dear Doctor / Dear Nurse" Letters, 1939-1946. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Article: Introduction to Omnis Orbis Warner, 1949. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Article: Untitled (on Narcotics 1949). (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Article: "The Sale I Never Forgot," in Printer's Ink, 1954. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Article: Introduction to 50 Years of Progress, 1928-1978. Hoffman-LaRoche, 1978. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Article: "The Lure of the Land of Bimini," "Maiden Voyage of Alisa III," "A New Company is Born.", undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Letters: To Dr. Barell. [Memoranda no.18-23, discussing Roche, Inc.] 1941. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Letters: To Mr. Handsman. (2 tls.) 1941, 1944. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Letter: "An Oscar to Mr. Bobst!" Letter to U.S. physicians in Medical Marketing, Dec. 1946 pg. 4. (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Letter: "On Medical Writing." M.D. Medical News Magazine, Mar. 1958 p.18. (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Report: Bobst-Columbia Plan for Pharmaceutical Education. 1957 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Unpublished: "A Legacy." [Housed with "Life is What You Make It," an autograph manuscript dated "May 3, 81."], undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Unpublished. Biographical data. n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - The death of Elmer Holmes Bobst. Newspaper clippings. Photocopy. 1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The death of Elmer Holmes Bobst. Newspaper clippings. Originals. 1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The Death of Elmer Holmes Bobst. News release. August, 1978. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Program for Burial Service. August 4, 1978. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Memorial Service for Elmer Holmes Bobst. Invitations and program. Sept. 13, 1978. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Memorial Service speech by Lane W. Adams, Sept. 13, 1978. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Memorial Service. Invitations list. Sept. 1978 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Memorial Service correspondence., undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Memorial Service list of attendees., undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - A - H. Letters of Condolence on the Death of Elmer Holmes Bobst., 1978 (Box 4)
  - I - Q. Letters of Condolence. Continuation., 1978 (Box 5)
  - R - Z. Letters of Condolence. Continuation., 1978 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Isaac Walton Bobst. 5 als. 1906, 1908. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Alice Holmes Bobst. 3 als. 1904 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Alice Holmes Bobst. 12 als. 1907 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Alice Holmes Bobst. 7 als. 1908, 1910, 1920. 1 als. 1920 [photocopy, 1920. EHB to AHB], 1908-1920 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Alice Holmes Bobst. An anthology of verse, Pictures of Memory, annotated by his mother for Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1912 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Bobst Family Members. 6 als. 1906-1908. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Ethel Rose Bobst and Elmer Holmes Bobst. 14 als. 1907 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Ethel Rose Bobst and Elmer Holmes Bobst. 8 als. 1908, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: High School Commencement Announcement. 1901 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Pennsylvania State Pharmaceutical Examining Board. 1906 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Pennsylvania State Board of Law Examiners. Admission to preliminary Bar exam. 1907, 1906-1908 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Political and Business Correspondence. 1940-1971. Hoffman-LaRoche. 1940-1944. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: U.S. Treasury Department. 1943-1944. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Fundraising Correspondence. 1943-1971. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Alfred T. Fuchs. 1946-1947 (Basle, Switzerland) (Box 8, Folder 4.1)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Warner-Hudnut. 1952-1954. (Box 8, Folder 4.2)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Warner/Chilcott. 1958 (Box 8, Folder 4.3)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: President and Mrs. Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1952-1954. [Includes letters from Press Secretary James Hagerty.] (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Alfred E. Driscoll, Governor of New Jersey. 1956 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Barnard M. Baruch. 1957, 1959. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: President Richard M. Nixon. 1958-1971. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: President John F. Kennedy from Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Robert H. Finch, Secretary of HEW. 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: John N. Mitchell, Attorney General. 1969 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: William P. Rogers, Secretary of State. 1970 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: John Tower, Senator. 1970 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Donald Schanche. 1971 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Social Invitations. 1969-1973. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Isaac W. Bobst Correspondence and Family Memorabilia. Isaac W. Bobst to Leah Bobst. 18als. 1862-1864, 1868, n.d., 1862-1868 (Box 9, Folder 1-5)
  - Isaac W. Bobst Correspondence and Family Memorabilia. Spoon used by Isaac W. Bobst while a Prisoner of War at Andersonville Prison. U.S. Civil War., 1864-1865 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Isaac W. Bobst Correspondence and Family Memorabilia. Isaac W. Bobst's Discharge from the Union Army, 1865., undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Isaac W. Bobst Correspondence and Family Memorabilia. Isaac W. Bobst In Memoriam. 1924 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Isaac W. Bobst Correspondence and Family Memorabilia. Joseph Holmes and Scotia Panner. Marriage License. 1851, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Isaac W. Bobst Correspondence and Family Memorabilia. Caroline M. Cox. Commonplace Book. 1859, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Bobst-Columbia Plan for Pharmaceutical Education. Report. January, 1957. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Bobst-Columbia Plan for Pharmaceutical Education. Pharmaceutical Education Symposium. Papers. January, 1957. (Box 10, Folder 2-8.)
  - Bobst-Columbia Plan for Pharmaceutical Education. Dinner in Honor of Elmer H. Bobst. June 1957. (Box 10, Folder 9-10.)
  - Bobst-Columbia Plan for Pharmaceutical Education. Wood, David A. Memoir: Elmer H. Bobst: A Man of the Century. November 1989. (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Series V: Film, Audio and Video Tape, Slides and Recordings.
  [Research copies may not be available for these materials yet. Check with the Fales archivist.]
  - Film, 16mm. Home Movies, ca. 1925-1949. [23 reels] (Box 1)
  - Film, 16mm. Home Movies, ca. 1950-1959. [audio-cassette 1 reel; master reel] (Box 2)
  - Film, 16mm. Newsreels, ca. 1939-1944. [7 reels] (Box 3)
  - Film, 16mm. Fit and Fair #35, sponsored by Richard Hudnut, n.d. [1 reel]; Unmarked. [9 reels], undated (Box 4)
  - Audio Cassette. Dr. Norman Vincent Peale. n.d. [2 cassettes], undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Audio Reel. Recorded May 12, 1971. [3 reels] (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Audio Reel. Dedication Ceremony, Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, New York University. Dec. 16, 1972. [3 reels] (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Copy of item 3., undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Video Tape. Bob Hope Promo. n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Video Cassette. Elmer Holmes Bobst Memorial Service. 1978 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Slides. Dedication Ceremony, Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, New York University. 1972 [4 plastic boxes] (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Amer Career Society. Million Club. n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - American Cancer Society Kick-off Show. [Elmer Holmes Bobst, Bob Hope, Frank Sinatra,et al.] 1947. (Box 6, Folder 1A.)
  - Cancer Drive. [Elmer Holmes Bobst] 1948. (Box 6, Folder 1B.)
  - International Association of Gerontology. [Elmer Holmes Bobst] 1951. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - American Cancer Society. [Elmer Holmes Bobst] 1953. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst Interview with H. Manning, Station CKGM, Montreal. 1960 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Gallatin Award, New York University. Part 1. 1966 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Gallatin Award. Part 2. 1966 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Hahneman Medical College and Hospital Dedication. Part 1., undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Hahneman Medical College and Hospital Dedication. Part 2., undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Audio Cassettes of Elmer Holmes Bobst and others. Various Public Addresses by Elmer Holmes Bobst. Side A. (1) Henry Morgan Show. Cancer Appeal. 1948 (2) Special American Show. 1950 (3) American Cancer Society. n.d. (4) "Cancer Control in America". U.S. State Dept. O.I.C. Side B. (1) "You and Medicine." CBS. 1951 (2) Pharmacy Week Program. 1947 (3) Elmer Holmes Bobst Talk on Mutual Broadcasting. 1947, 1947-1951 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Audio Cassettes of Elmer Holmes Bobst and others. Christmas Messages. Side A. Greetings from Elmer Holmes Bobst, 1950-1956, n.d. Side B. Mendelssohn. Musical Selections. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Audio Cassettes of Elmer Holmes Bobst and others. Presenting Personal Philosophies of Thoughtful People. Interviews by Edward R. Murrow. [Elmer Holmes Bobst et al.], undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Audio Cassettes of Elmer Holmes Bobst and others. If I'm Elected; The Actual Voices of Our Presidents and Their Opponents, 1892-1952. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Audio Cassettes of Elmer Holmes Bobst and others. President Richard M. Nixon. Inaugural Ceremonies. 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Series VI: Miscellaneous Items and Oversize.
  - Ship's bell from the yacht "Dodo.", undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Section of the ship's keel from the yacht "Alisa V.", undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - War memorabilia in Japanese box., undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ship's clock presented to Elmer Holmes Bobst., undated (Box 2)
  - Ship's barometer., undated (Box 3)
  - 1. Elmer Holmes Bobst. Portrait, framed. Circa 1940. 2. Roche, Inc. With an image of Elmer Holmes Bobst. Print, framed. By Dante V. DeFlorio. n.d. 3. University Heights, New York University. Print, framed. n.d. 4. (a.) Richard M. Nixon. Portrait. Circa 1940. (b.) National Cancer Advisory Board. Certificate. 1972. (c.) Obituary from The Record Express, Lititz, Pa. Aug. 10, 1978. 5. (a.) High School Diploma, Lititz, Pa. 1901. (b.) American Museum of Natural History. Lerner Marine Laboratory Fellowship Award. 1957. 6. Cruise of the "Alisa IV." Chart. 1951., 1901-1978 (Box loose items)
- Series VII: Monographs and Periodicals Belonging to Elmer Holmes Bobst.
  - ** Addison, Joseph. The Spectator. v. 8 London, 1738. ** Akimoto, S. Tokyo Miyage. Yokohama, 1912. ** Aristotle. Works. London, 1821. ** Art of Invigorating and Prolonging Life. Philadelphia, 1823. ** Bacon, Roger. The Cure of Old Age. London, 1638. ** Bible. [Holmes Family Bible, circa 1850.] ** Bible. [Inscription: Harry Bobst, Christmas, 1898.] ** Bible. New York, 1921. [Presentation: To Elmer Walton Bobst on his confirmation day by his grandfather, Isaac Bobst.] ** Chase, A.W. Chase's Recipes. Ann Arbor, Mi., 1866. ** Clough, S. DeWitt. Everyday Courage. Chicago, 1928. ** DeGomez. Persian Anecdotes. Trans. by Paul Chamberlain. London, 1730. ** Eisenhower, Julie Nixon. Eye on Nixon: A Photographic Study of the President and the Man. New York: Hawthorne Books, 1972. ** Everybody's Dictionary. ** Fishbein, Morris. The Medical Follies. New York, 1925. ** Guide to Jesus. Philadelphia, 1899. ** Harris, John. A History of the First Inventors of the World. London, 1686. ** How to Make a Drugstore Pay Better. Philadelphia, 1894. ** Jackson, Robert. A Treatise of the Fevers of Jamaica. Philadelphia, 1795. ** The Key to Heaven. Winterberg, N.Y., 1905. ** Lamb, Charles. The Essays of Elia. New York, 1892. ** LLoyd's Register of American Yachts. New York, 1954. ** Moore, George. Use of the Body in Relation to the Mind. New York, 1847. ** Omar Khayyam. The Rubaiyat. Portland, Me., 1894. ** Poppen, James L. Peron the Man. s.l., 1955. ** Powell, Thomas. Pocket Formulary and Physicians Manual. Savannah, Ga., 1955. ** Roche Review. Nutley, N.J. v.1-7; 1936-1943. ** Tales of the Genii. Trans. by Charles Morell. London, 1857. ** Wallace, William. Boating. New York, 1964. ** Webster's Little Gem Dictionary. Springfield, Mass. 1924 ** Webster's New International Unabridged Dictionary. Springfield, Mass. 1960 ** The Wedding Service. Philadelphia, n.d. ** Wilson, George. A Compleat Course of Chymistry. London, 1709. ** Wright, Isaac. Wright's Family Medicine. Madisonville, Tenn. 1833, 1638-1972 (Box loose items)
  - Periodicals: A selection of periodicals including articles about Elmer Holmes Bobst is housed in this series. The individual articles are listed and housed in folders in Series IV. ** 1. The Apothecary. v.58, no.1; 1946. ** 2. Better Impressions. v.2, no.1; 1952. ** 3. MD. v.2, no.3; 1958. ** 4. Monthly Magazine of the Oranges and Montclair. April, 1943. ** 5. NARD Journal. v.68, no.3; 1946. ** 6. Newsweek. v.52, no.9; 1958. ** 7. Printers' Ink. v.247, no.12; 1954. ** 8. Television Age. November, 1967. ** 9. Time. v.51, no.17; 1948. v.59, no.6; 1952. ** 10. The Warner Orbis. v.1, no.2; 1946., 1943-1967 (Box loose items)